<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WEBer Atelier</title>
    <description>Bullocks, I can&#39;t get any satisfaction.#end of line
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 08:56:46 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 08:56:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unity3D Importing Assets</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;unity3d-assets---fast-and-dirty&quot;&gt;UNITY3D Assets - Fast and Dirty&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assets created outside of Unity must be brought in to Unity by having the file either saved directly into the “Assets” 
folder of your project, or copied into that folder. For many common formats, you can save your source file directly 
into your project’s Assets folder and Unity will be able to read it. Unity will notice when you save new changes to the 
file and will re-import as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you create a Unity Project, you are creating a folder named after your project which contains the following subfolders:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MyUnityProject
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Assets  &amp;lt;——&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Library&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;obj&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;ProjectSettings&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Assets folder is where you should save or copy files that you want to use in your project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The contents of the Project Window in Unity shows the items in your Assets folder. So if you save or copy a file to your 
Assets folder, it will be imported and become visible in your Project Window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unity will automatically detect files as they are added to Assets folder, or if they are modified. When you put any asset 
into your Assets folder, you will see the asset appear in your Project View.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you drag a file into Unity’s Project Window from your computer (eg, from the Finder on Mac, or from Explorer on Windows), 
it will be copied into your Assets folder, and will appear in the Project window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The items you see in your Project window represent (in most cases) actual files on your computer, and if you delete 
them within Unity, you are deleting them from your computer too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;above image&lt;/em&gt; shows an example of a few  le and folders inside the Assets folder of a Unity project. You can create 
as many folders as you like and use them to organise your Assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll notice in the image above that there are .meta  les listed in the file system, but not visible in Unity’s Project Window. 
Unity creates these .meta files for each asset and folder, but they are hidden by default, so you may not see them in your Explorer/Finder either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They contain important information about how the asset is used in the project and they must stay with the asset 
file they relate to, so if you move or rename an asset file in Explorer/Finder, you must also move/rename the meta file to match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The simplest way to safely move or rename your assets is to always do it from within Unity’s project folder. 
This way, Unity will automatically move or rename the corresponding meta file. If you like, you can read more about .meta files 
and what goes on behind-the-scenes during the import process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to bring collections of assets into your project, you can use Asset Packages. See Asset Packages for more details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;common-types-of-assets&quot;&gt;Common Types of Assets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;image-files&quot;&gt;Image Files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most common image file types are supported, such as BMP, TIF, TGA, JPG, and PSD. If you save your layered Photoshop (.psd) files 
into your Assets folder, they will be imported as flattened images. You can find out more about importing images with alpha channels 
from photoshop, or importing your images as sprites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;d-model-files&quot;&gt;3D Model Files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you save your 3D files from most common 3D software packages in their native format (eg, .max, .blend, .mb, .ma) 
into your Assets folder, they will be imported by calling back to your 3D package’s FBX export plugin (*). Alternatively 
you can export as an FBX from your 3D app into your Unity project. Read more about importing 3D files from your 3D app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;meshes-and-animations&quot;&gt;Meshes and Animations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whichever 3D package you are using, Unity will import the meshes and animations from each file. For a list of applications that are 
supported by Unity, please see this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your mesh file does not need to have an animation to be imported. If you do use animations, you have your choice of importing all 
animations from a single file, or importing separate files, each with one animation. 
For more information about importing animations, please see of the Unity manual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;audio-files&quot;&gt;Audio Files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you save uncompressed audio files into your Assets folder, they will be imported according to the compression 
settings specified. Read more about importing audio files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;miscellaneous-asset-types&quot;&gt;Miscellaneous Asset Types&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In all cases, your original source file is never modified by Unity, even though within Unity you can often choose between various ways 
to compress, modify, or otherwise process the asset. The import process reads your source file, and creates a game-ready representation 
of your asset internally, matching your chosen import settings. If you modify the import settings for an asset, or make a change to the 
source file in the Asset folder, will cause Unity to re-import the asset again to reflect your new changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: Importing native 3D formats requires the 3D application to be installed on the same computer as Unity. This is because Unity uses 
the 3D application’s FBX exporter plug-in to read the file. Alternatively, you can directly export as FBX from your application and save 
into the Projects folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;importing-settings&quot;&gt;Importing Settings&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each type of asset that Unity supports has a set of Import Settings, which affect how the asset appears or behaves. To view an asset’s 
import settings, select the asset in the Project View. The import settings for this asset will appear in the Inspector. The options that 
are displayed will vary depending on the type of asset that is selected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, the import settings for an image will allow you to choose whether it’s imported as a texture, a 2D sprite, or a normal map. 
The import settings for an FBX file allow you to adjust the scale, generate normals or lightmap coordinates, and split &amp;amp; trim animation 
clips defined in the file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For other asset types, the import settings will look different. The various settings you see will relate to the type of asset selected. 
Here’s an example of an Audio asset, with its related import settings shown in the inspector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are developing a cross-platform project, you can override the “default” settings and assign different import settings on a 
per-platform basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;importing-the-asset-store&quot;&gt;Importing the Asset Store&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Unity Asset Store is home to a growing library of free and commercial assets created both by Unity Technologies and also members 
of the community. A wide variety of assets is available, covering everything from textures, models and animations to whole project 
examples, tutorials and Editor extensions. The assets are accessed from a simple interface built into the Unity Editor and are 
downloaded and imported directly into your project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unity users can become publishers on Asset Store, and sell content they have created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can open the Asset Store window by selecting Window-&amp;gt;AssetStore from the main menu. On your first visit, you will be prompted 
to create a free user account which you will use to access the Store subsequently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;photo needed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1   To the right of these are buttons for viewing the Download Manager and for viewing the current contents of your shopping cart.
2   The Download Manager allows you to view the packages you have already bought and also to find and install any updates. 
Additionally, the standard packages supplied with Unity can be viewed and added to your project with the same interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;location-of-downloaded-asset-files&quot;&gt;Location of Downloaded Asset Files&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will rarely, if ever, need to access the files downloaded from the Asset Store directly. However, if you do need to, you can 
find them in the following Windows directory:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;~/Library/Unity/Asset Store&lt;/code&gt; and then on the Mac and in:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;C:\Users\accountName\AppData\Roaming\Unity\Asset Store&lt;/code&gt; …on Windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These folders contain subfolders that correspond to particular Asset Store vendors - the actual asset  les are contained in the 
appropriate subfolders.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 17:00:37 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/tech/unity-import-assets</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/tech/unity-import-assets</guid>
        
        <category>unity3d</category>
        
        <category>3D</category>
        
        <category>design</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        <category>programming</category>
        
        <category>gaming</category>
        
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Urban Agriculture in Confined Spaces - Part I</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;reactjs-development&quot;&gt;Reactjs Development&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/res/js/react-dom-0.14.7.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;/res/js/react-game.jsx&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 16:00:37 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/tech/react-game</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/tech/react-game</guid>
        
        <category>reactjs</category>
        
        <category>gaming</category>
        
        <category>webdevelopment</category>
        
        <category>javascript</category>
        
        <category>DOM</category>
        
        <category>programming</category>
        
        <category>gaming</category>
        
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Urban Agriculture in Confined Spaces - Part I</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;urban-agriculture-in-confined-spaces---part-i&quot;&gt;Urban Agriculture in Confined Spaces - Part I&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the advent of yet another spring season in the Northern Hemisphere. Sorry to all our antipodals, but it is
yet another wonderful opportunity to get experimental with &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Greening&lt;/code&gt;, which is a slang jargon word for enjoying
the hobby of producing decorative and or healthy plants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this multipart series, we will be looking over options within a limited urban environment. As time marches on
and technology improves things, while still not seeing the true full ramifications of the decisions now made, it
would actually be quiet a good safety net for all of us to consider growing nearly anything. I just heard a shout-out
from the Rastas and others out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the subjects that will be covered in this series are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Small Space Veggie Gardens: The Perks &amp;amp; Ground Rules&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Types of Small Space Gardens&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Time-Saving Tips&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to Grow the More Popular Veggies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, we could possibly go into growing tomatoes, but in all likelihood, this narrator will not traverse that
path due to his own aversions. Having moved from a western equatorial climate with sun, heat and humidity to the
Northern section of another continent did not stifle the human inclination to grow the things they love and often
personally use. One year, I went all out to try and grow 30 tomato plants of varying breeds. The lack of sun,
due to coastal over-cast skies and lower temperatures, I harvested 5 small red tomatoes that year, and 5 crates
of green tomatoes with black mold spots marking their end. Meh, for nostalgia, perhaps we will include tomatoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greening, health and perhaps mostly due to the pleasure of endowing our children with a rudimentary understanding
of how to provide for themselves in an unforeseeable future gives me the satisfactory feeling accustom to being
a father.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 06:00:37 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/agriculture/growing-in-confined-spaces</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/agriculture/growing-in-confined-spaces</guid>
        
        <category>agriculture</category>
        
        <category>ecology</category>
        
        
        <category>agriculture</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 22:00:37 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/jekyll/welcome-to-jekyll</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2016/jekyll/welcome-to-jekyll</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
